let's look at the answer to our locality
quiz we were asked which of these are
not good examples of locality the
statement that he trained three times
today so it will likely rain today again
is a decent example of locality usually
if it rained often it's probably gonna
just continue raining often for a while
we ate dinner at 6:00 every day last
week so probably we will eat dinner
around 6:00 this week too this also
tends to be true people tend to eat
meals around the same time for a while
and finally it was New Year's Eve
yesterday so it will probably be New
Year's Eve today too this one is not a
good example of vocality why well
because some things do not have locality
for example it being New Year's Eve one
day usually means that the next day it
won't be New Year's Eve because New
Year's Eve is one of those things that
do not have much locality if it was
yesterday then we know it's not gonna be
today which is kind of opposite of what
the locality principle is about as we
can see some things do have the locality
property and some things do not